So, listen, we're very excited in terms
of how night one um concluded for us to
get um you know, two of kind of what I
would call our our short list players um
to pick up uh another top 100 pick as
well as another pick in the top 150. Um
you know, we were very pleased with with
um just really all the activity this
evening. We're really excited about
Spencer um you know, and his potential
at left tackle. He's super athletic,
very versatile, uh elite, you know,
makeup. And then KC, he's um you know,
he's dynamic. He's uh you know, an
outstanding separator, really good with
the ball in his hands. Uh honestly,
probably the best punt returner in this
class. And you know, those two guys will
will really help our offense moving
forward. So with that, open up for
questions.
>> It was and uh you know, we were joking.
It's like, okay, well, the board
probably fell better than it did in our
simulations in the in the week leading
up to it, which is always nice. Um, but
we we're really excited about the two
players uh that we got and we're really
excited that um you know, we were able
to pick up the extra draft resources
while, you know, taking the player that
we really coveted at nine. Andrew, how
many did you get a lot of calls for six
or and Casey was the best one or or you
know,
>> how' that kind of go when you're on the
clock?
>> We did get several calls for six. Um,
you know, we thought through um I I
should say this, we got several calls uh
for six and nine, the combination of six
and nine. um at six. Um you know, Kansas
City made the made the most sense
because it was a big enough move where
we could pick up resources. Um but also
small enough with what had happened on
the board that, you know, we could we
could get um you know, one of our short
list of of targets of which, you know,
Spencer was at the top. Um and then at
nine, we did get a little bit of action
there as well. Um but nothing that
necessarily compelled us to move off of
the pick. I know I know you kind of
believe the tackle is tackle, but in
Spencer's case, does it help that you've
seen him play on the left side?
>> Yeah, you know, it c it certainly helps.
Um, but really you're looking more for
traits in that regard, Dan, just
because, you know, if you think about
it, we move guys from the left side to
the right side all the time and it never
gets talked about. Um, and that
distinction, it's just, you know, you
need two of them to pass protect and one
you maybe help a little, the other you
help a little bit more. Um, but Spencer,
he's he's super athletic. He's he's
played on both sides. He's really smart.
We're excited to have him.
>> Hey, Andrew. And Andrew, uh Casey had
some drops and uh are you concerned
about about that?
>> Yeah, every receiver besides maybe Larry
Fitzgerald has a couple drops and um you
know, Casey, he's been a dynamic
producer at NC State, Texas&M.
Um you know, he he's he's electric with
the ball in his hands and uh we're
looking forward to having him.
um this offseason you know Spencer the
versatility that he has. Um was that
really intentional for you this off
season with maybe what has happened with
the offensive line the last couple
years? It just feels like versatility
was like a top your wish list for every
player that you brought in in that
position.
>> I'd say if you're on the O line you you
typically need to be able to play two
spots. I'd say probably more so than
versatility, it was resiliency within
the O line in terms of how you build
that position group. Um, versatility is
one way to do it. Strength and numbers
is is another way to do it. Um, you
know, I think we'll be in a position
where we have both. You know, with
Spencer in particular, look, we're
looking to park him at left tackle and
let him play. So, um, while it's nice
that he's played several spots, that's
not our vision for him.
>> Um, I know he played inside and out. Do
you envision him being able to play both
roles for you? Yeah, we do.
>> We talked to him and read the letters
that he wrote. Um just how impressive it
is that able to get where he has given
all he's grown up with, including the
start.
>> Yeah, that's one that's one thing that
we talked about. I I told him um you
know, when he was on his his 30 visit, I
think it's incredible what he's what
he's overcome and gone through in his
life. Um when when we got the uh you
know, his agent sent sent the letter,
I'm sure, to you know, every GM, but um
I actually went I I called him after the
letter. I was like, "Hey, look, I I
thought that was really awesome." And
that that was separate from, you know,
obviously liking him as a prospect, but
um you I told I'll share one story when
Casey visited. I was like, "Hey, I hope
you're a Brown, but if you're not, I
sure hope you're in the NFC because I
don't want to face you." And then I told
his agent afterwards was, "Look, hey,
everything that that kid's about,
everything that he's overcome, um you
know, if he's not here, he just needs to
know he's got a fan. Just I I really
love the person." Um and he's obviously
a dynamic football player. Was his punt
return ability just a bonus or did it
put him over the top among other
receivers left?
>> I'd say it was a I'd say it was a bonus,
you know, more than anything, Tony,
because um it's certainly great if you
can, you know, if you can get the ball
and play Marcus in a variety of ways. It
allows you to be more explosive as a
team, allows you to score more points.
Uh but also being realistic that you
know if you look at former let's say
high pick receivers whether it's you
Deshawn Jackson back in the day Dez
Bryan early in his career you know
usually at some point they probably like
play their way off of that. So like it's
not necessarily bankable for their
entire career. Um but with Casey it
certainly was an added bonus.
>> Obviously you had Spencer
number one amongst your targets but did
you give much thought to Jordan Tyson
was you know a little call at that
moment to trade away from him at all or
did you know that you were targeting
Spencer?
>> You know, we we liked a number of those
guys up there, including Jordan. Um, you
know, but but Spencer was our really
really our top, excuse me, Spencer was
our top target at that point.
>> Um, a lot was made about Spencer's arm
length. Um, I was curious when you
watched the film, how much that was like
a a talking point and then what are the
the traits that you think will allow
that to not be be an issue in the NFL?
Yeah, I know it gets talked about a lot
and I remember, you know, the, you know,
the legendary, you know, O line coach,
uh, Dante Scarnia with New England used
to say it's just, it's way overrated. I
think most times tackles get beat for a
lack of feet or athleticism or anchor or
awareness, you know, as opposed to
length. Um, the biggest thing is like,
hey, how can the guys, you know, shorten
the corner? And with elite athletes like
Spencer, they do it with their movement
skills. Maybe if you have a guy that
just is not as quick or not as agile,
then length is a little bit more
important. Um, but the difference in his
success isn't going to be, you know,
this in terms of in terms of arm length.
He has a number of incredible um both
physical and mental characteristics that
we think will lead to a successful
transition.
>> How do you measure when you have like a
dynam dynamic athlete like Casey, but
guys drop ball, guys drop balls.
>> How do you kind of measure that? Yeah,
it it's it's it's really relative to the
population. Like I know that gets you
know that gets talked about, but he has
natural dexterity. Um, you know, it's
nothing it's nothing extreme or nothing
out of um uh
I guess it's not an it's not an outlier,
you know, relative to to other receivers
in the draft class. I know that's been
the primary talking point, but we're
we're comfortable with Casey's hands.
>> Said he drove to Cleveland from Indie.
Was he in fact your first 30 visit?
Uh, great question, Tony.
I don't know if he was our first. He was
among our first. Um, but we had we had a
couple of guys in right after the right
after the combine. He was one of them. I
I don't I don't think he was the very
first, but he was among our first. Yes.
>> Did you
>> Let me go Mary Kay and then I'll go
Zach. Do you envision using all of the
remaining draftings that you have now
that you picked up the
>> Look, I I would hope to draft in volume
this year, but it really just depends on
how the board falls. So, I'm I'm also
like depending on how good of a review
you guys write us. I'm going to use that
seventh rounder if you guys write
something. I think Okay.
>> Did Todd and you to an extent see some Z
Flowers and how Todd used him? You know,
I do think there are I do think there
are some similarities in terms of like
the movement skills, the twitch.
Honestly, some of the questions
regarding the hands coming out, you
know, Terry. Um, you know, I think the
one thing that maybe gets a little bit
lost is like Ki is a much bigger uh, you
know, player than Z, but I think there
is some overlap in the characteristics.
Um, you know, I think, you know, look,
if we get a player who's comparable to Z
Flowers, you know, when we're sitting
here from three years, we'll be elated.
>> Let's go back to Spencer. I mean, How
early on in this process had you guys
really zeroed in on him as the top
tackle in a pretty deep class?
>> You know, we we used the whole process,
Ashley. You know, we we did feel like
Spencer was, you know, unique in terms
of, you know, everything that comprised
his um onfield performance, his physical
skills, and and his makeup. Um but, you
know, we we do like to use the whole
shot clock. the terms of the trade with
KC. Was it an option to get a 2027 pick?
>> No. No.
>> Wanted an extra third round pick
>> there. There was no option or discussion
of future picks.
>> I know it wind up only being two picks
that you didn't know. Um what's that
nervous level like saying, "Okay, you
want Spencer, but there's a chance." I
mean, were you worried at all that seven
and eight could take him?
>> You know, that's part of the risk. got,
you know, when we were on the clock at
six, you know, what I told the room is,
hey, there are there are really kind of
three guys left that, you know, we'd be
elated with, you know, if we had to sit
and pick. Um, moving back three spots
and having an idea of of where Kansas
City was going, we knew we were going to
get one of those three guys. Um, we also
felt the teams behind us, you know,
Washington, you know, they extended
Tonsel, they drafted Josh Connorly in
the first round last year. Um, New
Orleans, they drafted Kelvin Banks, you
know, at nine last year and then Fuaga
the year before that. So, we felt pretty
comfortable that a tackle wasn't going
to go unless a team traded into it. But
if one did, you know, we we we felt good
with the group of players that were in
front of us.
>> Able to contain his excitement upstairs
with get him. Uh,
>> I'm sorry. I didn't I didn't see hear
you mention
>> Todd's reaction upstairs, you know, the
first round. Was he able to contain his
excitement?
>> He was he was pretty pumped up. He was
pretty pumped up. So, we we all were um,
you know, look, you don't always have
the board, you know, fall away that you
that you predict. And look, the idea is
like, you know, these guys, they still
have to they haven't hit the grass. They
still have to perform at our level. But
it's, you know, it's it's a it's a start
that we are excited about because of the
players and the people.
He me Spencer mentioned Joe uh Thomas
and just how much he looks up to him and
everything. How much are you guys going
to try to do you try to fac you know
facilitate getting those two together?
You know I know Joe's got his own
schedule and everything but how much do
you try to get those two together?
>> Yeah, you know Joe's Joe's obviously one
of our distinguished alumnists and he's
he's always um you know involved in in
in our O linemen. Um, also there's
there's a connection with with Joe and
um, you know, Spencer's, you know,
representation. But, you know, we we
love I think you all know we love having
Joe around here and everything like
that. Uh, I'm sure he will have words of
wisdom for for Spencer and um, you know,
that's definitely a connection we will
look to make.
>> Let me go here first, Jeff, and then
I'll come back to you.
>> You obviously talked so much leading up
to the draft just about not being, you
know, crippled by needs versus best
player available. Sort of that strategy.
um when when push came to show,
especially when you were on the clock at
six, like how were those what were those
conversations like and sort of deciding
what was there and what your needs were?
Because it turned out you obviously did
end up addressing some of your bigger
needs tonight.
>> There really wasn't a ton of
conversation. You know, all those
conversations happened beforehand. Like
at this point, it's like I would almost
make the quote of like calling plays.
You you talk through all those different
scenarios ahead of time. Um, and this
one was straightforward because, um, you
know, we viewed Spencer as one of the
top prospects in the draft. So, um, it
it made it pretty easy. There was, you
know, we didn't really feel like there
was a any type of trade-off in that
regard. Go ahead, Jeff.
>> Can you just reflect, Andrew, on how
you've rebuilt the offensive line here
in these last two months? Yeah, I I
think we are very excited about the
players that we've brought in as well as
the development that's occurring with,
you know, existing players. Um, you
know, obviously the, you know, the vets
that that we acquired, whether it's via
trade or or free agency or, you know,
with the cap cut, um, we felt like we've
we've
brought quality production, um, you
know, as well as as experience to that
group. Um, and then obviously with night
one adding Spencer, we think that's a,
you know, a big, um, you know,
foundational foundational piece to that
position group. Um, we'll see where we
go from here. Look, we still have nine
more picks. Um, you know, we may not be
done, you know, with the O line at that
point. Um, and like I said, we're
excited about uh, some of our younger
guys that are going to get greater
opportunities, but um, it's a good
start.
You've talked about the traits with
Spencer, but I know to be a great O
line, there's some personality aspects,
right? Some nasty that the guy has to
have. Can you sort of speak to that side
of Spencer and what you guys learned
about him? Yeah, I think one of the cool
things about Spencer is you you can you
look at how um I guess scheme
transcendent he's been because what they
did his uh in 24 versus 25 was a lot
honestly was like a lot different in
terms of how they structured the run
game, how they did, you know, past pro
and um you can see him move, you can see
him maul. Um, I think he's he's very
gifted and very versatile in that
regard. And um, you know, don't be
fooled by his kindness when you meet
him. Have you guys done your Zoom with
him already? Yeah. Don't be fooled by
his kindness. He's he's he's he's nasty
on the field. So,